Streib, Victor; Papers apap330
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Case Files, 1947-2012, Undated; 1; 19 cubic ft.
  - Executed Juveniles, United States, 1982-2007, Undated; 1.3; 4 cubic ft.
    - Kentucky: William Carson Gray, executed 1943-06-25, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 142)
    - Kentucky: John Hicks, executed 1882-02-24, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 143)
    - Kentucky: Earl Thompson, executed 1910-01-07, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 144)
    - Kentucky: Silas Williams, executed 1913-03-21, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 145)
    - Kentucky: Herbert Workman, executed 1949-03-04, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 146)
    - Kentucky: Arthur Jones, executed 1946-03-22, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 147)
    - Kentucky: George Magee, executed 1895-02-23, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 148)
    - Kentucky: Allen Mathis, executed 1906-07-25, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 149)
    - Kentucky: William Miller, executed 1899-02-03, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 150)
    - Kentucky: Claude O' Brien, executed 1903-07-24, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 151)
    - Kentucky: Burnett Sexton, executed 1943-01-15, 1985; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 152)
    - Kentucky: William Henry Stepter, executed 1847-06-05, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 153)
    - Louisiana: James Bessar and Wilbert Powell, executed 1948-04-23, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 154)
    - Louisiana: Lucius Carter, executed 1917-11-09, 2007 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 155)
    - Louisiana: Jim Conelm, executed 1888-02-03, 1984; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 1)
    - Louisiana: George Cotton, executed 1914-11-06, 1995; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 2)
    - Louisiana: Willie Francis, executed 1947-06-07, 1984; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 3)
    - Louisiana: Slave Frank, executed 1855-10-15, 1995; 2007; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 4)
    - Louisiana: Slave Joseph, executed 1858-06-15, 1995; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 5)
    - Louisiana: Irvin Mattio, executed 1948-01-09, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 6)
    - Louisiana: Joe Persons, executed 1915-09-24, 2007 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 7)
    - Louisiana: Dalton Prejean, executed 1990-05-18, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 8)
    - Louisiana: Dalton Prejean, executed 1990-05-18, 1991 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 9)
    - Louisiana: Dalton Prejean, executed 1990-05-18, 1991 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 10)
    - Louisiana: Dalton Prejean, executed 1990-05-18 Application for stay of execution, 1989 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 11)
    - Louisiana: Dalton Prejean, executed 1990-05-18 Application for stay of execution, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 12)
    - Louisiana: Dalton Prejean, executed 1990-05-18 Petition for post conviction relief, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 13)
    - Louisiana: Dalton Prejean, executed 1990-05-18 Petition for post conviction relief, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 14)
    - Louisiana: Henry Riley, executed 1945-12-07, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 15)
    - Louisiana: Wesley Turner, executed 1878-04-22, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 16)
    - Louisiana: Lewis Young, executed 1907-10-11, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 17)
    - Maryland: John Berny, executed 1899-06-16, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 18)
    - Maryland: Dennis Sommerfield, executed 1898-28-12, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 19)
    - Maryland: Carroll Gibson, executed 1925-02-13, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 20)
    - Maryland: Weldon Jones, executed 1947-08-01, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 21)
    - Maryland: Wiley Kirk, executed 1901-05-31, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 22)
    - Maryland: William Lee, executed 1906-07-26, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 23)
    - Maryland: Wish Shepard, executed 1915-08-27, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 24)
    - Maryland: Leonard Melvin Shockley, executed 1959-04-10, 1984; 1985; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 25)
    - Maryland: Mary Wallis, executed 1891-02-10, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 26)
    - Maryland: Medford Waters executed 1879-12-05, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 27)
    - Massachusetts: General, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 28)
    - Massachusetts: Bristol, executed 1763-12-01, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 29)
    - Massachusetts: Stephen Clark, executed 1804-08-20, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 30)
    - Massachusetts: Paul Giacomazza, 1984; 1985; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 31)
    - Massachusetts: Lee Gong, executed 1909-10-12, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 32)
    - Massachusetts: Benjamin Courd, executed 1674-04-02, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 33)
    - Massachusetts: Thomas Granger, executed 1642, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 34)
    - Massachusetts: James Edwand Nowlin, executed 1888-01-20, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 35)
    - Massachusetts: Ezra Ross, executed 1778-07-02, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 36)
    - Minnesota: Peter Barrett, executed 1889-03-22, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 37)
    - Minnesota: Timothy Barrett, executed 1889-03-22, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 38)
    - Mississippi: General, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 39)
    - Mississippi: James Lewis and Charles Trudell, executed 1947-07-23, 1984; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 40)
    - Mississippi: Arthur Moore, executed 1950-01-26, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 41)
    - Mississippi: Cleveland Nelson, executed 1931-05-08, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 42)
    - Mississippi: James Newson, Jr. executed 1944-03-24, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 43)
    - Mississippi: George Owens, executed 1937-01-20, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 44)
    - Mississippi: Elija Parker, executed 1943-07-01, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 45)
    - Mississippi: Joe Phillips, executed 1937-01-20, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 46)
    - Mississippi: John West Pulliam, executed 1950-05-25, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 47)
    - Mississippi: Henry Washington, executed 1880-12-31, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 48)
    - Missouri: General, 1991; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 49)
    - Missouri: William Barton, executed 1880-03-26, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 50)
    - Missouri: Frederick Lashley, executed 1993-07-28, 1985; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 51)
    - Missouri: Lawrence Mabry, executed 1930-01-31, 1990; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 52)
    - Missouri: Phillip Martin, executed 1895-02-15, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 53)
    - Missouri: Slave Mary, executed 1838-09-30, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 54)
    - Missouri: James Reed, executed 1899-03-30, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 55)
    - Missouri: Peter Schmidt, executed 1897-02-16, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 56)
    - Missouri: Charles Talbot, executed 1881-07-22, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 57)
    - Missouri: William Walker, executed 1889-05-10, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 58)
    - Montana: Frank Roberts, executed 1878-10-31, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 59)
    - Montana: William Rhea, executed 1903-07-10, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 60)
    - Nebraska: General, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 61)
    - Nevada: Rufus Anderson, executed 1868-10-30, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 62)
    - Nevada: David Blackwell, executed 1949-04-2, 1985; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 63)
    - Nevada: Floyd Loveless, executed 1944-09-29, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 64)
    - Nevada: Fred Roberts, executed 1905-11-17, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 65)
    - Nevada: Abraham Prescott, executed 1836-01-06, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 66)
    - New Jersey: James Guild, executed 1829-11-28, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 67)
    - New Jersey: Rosan Keen, executed 1844-04-26, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 68)
    - New Jersey: Richard Sparks, executed 1915-01-05, 1983; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 69)
    - New Jersey: Howard Sullivan, executed 1884-12-02, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 70)
    - New Mexico: Romero, executed 1883-02-02, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 71)
    - New York: General, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 72)
    - New York: Octavius Baron, executed 1838-07-25, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 73)
    - New York: Lew Bing, executed 1944-08-31, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 74)
    - New York: Cosimo Bresica, executed 1926-08-26, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 75)
    - New York: William Byers, executed 1956-01-12, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 76)
    - New York: Edward Deacons, executed 1888-07-10, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 77)
    - New York: Benitez DeJesus, executed 1943-07-08, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 78)
    - New York: George Denny, executed 1844-07-26, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 79)
    - New York: William Diaz, executed 1943-07-08, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 80)
    - New York: Lawrence Edwards, executed 1942-09-17, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 81)
    - New York: Frederick Fowler, executed 1937-01-21, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 82)
    - New York: John Garguila, executed 1926-07-09, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 83)
    - New York: Dominic Guariglia, executed 1939-01-26, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 84)
    - New York: Edward Haight, executed 1943-07-08, 1984; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 1)
    - New York: Elmer Hyatt, executed 1920-07-29, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 2)
    - New York: Jauvhan Jackson, executed 1948-01-09, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 3)
    - New York: Henry Matthews, executed 1955-02-10, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 4)
    - New York: Stanley Pluzdrak, executed 1935-04-25, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 5)
    - New York: Norman Roye, executed 1956-01-09, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 6)
    - New York: John Tuhi, executed 1817-07-25, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 7)
    - North Carolina: General, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 8)
    - North Carolina: Arnold, executed 1852-05-13, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 9)
    - North Carolina: Will Black, executed 1916-04-02, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 10)
    - North Carolina: John Broadnax, executed 1903-04-17, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 11)
    - North Carolina: Nathaniel Bryant, executed 1940-02-16, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 12)
    - North Carolina: McIver Burnette, executed 1922-10-12, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 13)
    - North Carolina: Will Carter, executed 1983-09-28 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 14)
    - North Carolina: John Lewis Edwards, executed 1934-07-07, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 15)
    - North Carolina: Kenneth Hale, executed 1925-01-05, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 16)
    - North Carolina: Otis Harris, executed 1942-10-30, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 17)
    - North Carolina: L.J. Jefferson, executed 1938-09-23, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 18)
    - North Carolina: George McNair, executed 1886-06-01, 1985 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 19)
    - North Carolina: Larny McNeill, executed 1937-08-13, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 20)
    - North Carolina: William Monroe, executed 1901-09-13, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 21)
    - North Carolina: William Perry, executed 1937-12-10, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 22)
    - North Carolina: Ralph Thompson, executed 1944-12-29, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 23)
    - North Carolina: Freddie Willey, executed 1929-06-28, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 24)
    - North Carolina: Calvin williams, executed 1946-12-13, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 25)
    - Ohio: General, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 26)
    - Ohio: Lee Akers, executed 1930-06-13, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 27)
    - Ohio: Harley Beard, executed 1914-12-04, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 28)
    - Ohio: James Coleman, executed 1928-02-07, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 29)
    - Ohio: John Coverson, executed 1928-01-10, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 30)
    - Ohio: Donald Frohner, executed 1948-08-20, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 31)
    - Ohio: William Haas, executed 1897-04-21, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 32)
    - Ohio: Henry William Hagert, executed 1945-10-03, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 33)
    - Ohio: Louis Vernon Hand, executed 1944-01-14, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 34)
    - Ohio: Floyd Hewitt, executed 1928-01-06, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 35)
    - Ohio: Otto Leuth, executed 1890-08-29, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 36)
    - Ohio: George Mann, executed 1880-06-25, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 37)
    - Ohio: Joseph Murphy, executed 1933-08-14, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 38)
    - Ohio: Gustave Ohr, executed 1880-06-26, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 39)
    - Ohio: Sam Pupera, executed 1922-05-09, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 40)
    - Ohio: Emanuel Ross, executed 1926-11-26, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 41)
    - Ohio: John Sammett, executed 1880-06-25, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 42)
    - Ohio: Bernard Schreiber, executed 1956-03-15, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 43)
    - Ohio: William Taylor, executed 1895-07-26, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 44)
    - Ohio: Pang Young, executed 1939-07-12, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 45)
    - Oklahoma: general, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 46)
    - Oklahoma: Mitchell Aderson, executed 1885-05-06, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 47)
    - Oklahoma: Alan Scott Hain, executed 2003-04-03, 1988; 1944; 2001 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 48)
    - Oklahoma: Saphire Barehead, executed 1885-08-04, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 49)
    - Oklahoma: Sean Sellers, executed 1999-02-04, 1986; 1998 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 50)
    - Oregon: Lloyd Montgomery, executed 1896-01-31, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 51)
    - Oregon: John Anthony Soto, executed 1941-09-25, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 52)
    - Pennsylvania: William Battin, executed 1722-08-15, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 53)
    - Pennsylvania: James Burke, executed 1784-10-16, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 54)
    - Pennsylvania: Dominick Digeso, executed 1916-12-04, 1982; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 55)
    - Pennsylvania: Reese Evans, executed 1853-09-09, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 56)
    - Pennsylvania: Stanley Marcavice, executed 1909-11-18, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 57)
    - Pennsylvania: Rosario Sergi, executed 1908-07-11, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 58)
    - Pennsylvania: Lewellyn Stout, executed 1899-08-22, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 59)
    - Pennsylvania: Alexander Williams, executed 1931-06-08, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 60)
    - Rhode Island: Hannah Degoe, executed 1710-11-29, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 61)
    - South Carolina: Robert Ashley, executed 1936-06-26, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 62)
    - South Carolina: Batteau (Bennett), executed 1822-07-21, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 63)
    - South Carolina: Milbry Brown, executed 1892-10-07, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 64)
    - South Carolina: Frank Dash, Jr., executed 1940-01-19, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 65)
    - South Carolina: Edinburgh, executed 1826-03-20, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 66)
    - South Carolina: John ellis, executed 1934-04-27, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 67)
    - South Carolina: Frank Green, executed 1913-04-04, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 68)
    - South Carolina: Edward Holmes, executed 1879-11-21, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 69)
    - South Carolina: Matthew Jamison, executed 1948-12-03, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 70)
    - South Carolina: Thomas Johnson, executed 1923-02-02, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 71)
    - South Carolina: William Johnson, executed 1905-06-16, 1983 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 72)
    - South Carolina: Armstead Jones, executed 1890-07-11, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 73)
    - South Carolina: Reuben Jones, executed 1934-07-20, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 74)
    - South Carolina: George Kenny, executed 1908-01-18, 1982 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 75)
    - South Carolina: James Terry Roach, executed 1986-01-10, 1984; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 76)
    - South Carolina: George Stinney, executed 1944-06-16, 1986; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 77)
    - Tennessee: Clarence Cox, executed 1894-12-22, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 78)
    - Tennessee: William Dwight, executed 1922-07-25, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 79)
    - Tennessee: George Howell, executed 1878-09-05, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 80)
    - Tennessee: Cyrenac Jackson and Taylor Neal, executed 1921-08-03, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 81)
    - Tennessee: Fred Jackson, executed 1947-08-11, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 82)
    - Tennessee: Walter Kennedy, executed 1936-01-21, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 83)
    - Tennessee: George Mapp, executed 1895-01-11, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 84)
    - Tennessee: John Presswood, Jr., executed 1872-05-24, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 85)
    - Tennessee: Robert Gamble's Slave, executed 1818, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 86)
    - Tennessee: Leo Temples, executed 1912-12-19, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 87)
    - Tennessee: Ernest Womack, executed 1936-04-10, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 88)
    - Texas: general, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 89)
    - Texas: Alke Taylor, executed 1879-08-22, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 90)
    - Texas: James Bailey, executed 1904-09-26, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 91)
    - Texas: Napolean Beazley, executed 2002-05-28, 2001; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 92)
    - Texas: Henry Brown, executed 1900-05-07, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 93)
    - Texas: Jackson Bunch, executed 1856-11-21, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 94)
    - Texas: Mark Henry Calhoun, executed 1938-06-17, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 95)
    - Texas: Joe Cannon, executed 1998-04-22, 1986; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 96)
    - Texas: Ruben Cantu, executed 1993-08-24, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 97)
    - Texas: Robert Anthony Carter, executed 1998-05-18, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 98)
    - Texas: Buck Chappell, executed 1896-03-18, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 99)
    - Texas: Otto Clear, executed 1924-09-12, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 100)
    - Texas: James Echols, executed 1964-05-07, 1984; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 1)
    - Texas: Jose Flores, executed 1921-07-21, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 2)
    - Texas: Frank Johnny Garrett, executed 1992-02-11, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 3)
    - Texas: Monk Gibson, executed 1908-06-28, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 4)
    - Texas: Gary Graham, ex .2000-06-22 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 5)
    - Texas: Gary Graham, ex .2000-06-22 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 6)
    - Texas: John L. Green, executed 1932-08-05, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 7)
    - Texas: Paul Curtis Harris, executed 1993-07-02, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 8)
    - Texas: Silas Jarman, executed 1929-05-24, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 9)
    - Texas: Adrian Johnson, executed 1962-04-19, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 10)
    - Texas: John Andrew Johnson, executed 1888-12-21, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 11)
    - Texas: J.T. Jones, executed 2002-08-08 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 12)
    - Texas: Leon Cardenas Martinez, executed 1914-05-11, 1984; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 13)
    - Texas: Glen Mcginnis, executed, 2000 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 14)
    - Texas: Gerald Lee Mitchell, executed 2001-10-22, 1993; 2007 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 15)
    - Texas: Buster Northern, executed 1949-04-16, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 16)
    - Texas: Toronto Patterson, executed 2002-08-28 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 17)
    - Texas: Peter, executed 1859-01-27, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 18)
    - Texas: Jay Kelly Pinkerton, executed 1986-05-15, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 19)
    - Texas: Charles F. Rumbaugh, executed 1985-09-11, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 20)
    - Texas: Alex Spencer, executed 1903-04-10, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 21)
    - Texas: John Taylor, executed 1907-11-22, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 22)
    - Texas: Alberto Vargas, executed 1907-01-04, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 23)
    - Texas: Federico Sanchez, executed 1915-03-03, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 24)
    - Texas: Clarence Thomas, executed 1933-12-15, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 25)
    - Texas: David Williams, executed 1944-07-09, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 26)
    - Utah: Chauncey Millard, executed 1869-01-29, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 27)
    - Vermont: Henry Welcome, executed 1871-01-20, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 28)
    - Virginia: General, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 29)
    - Virginia: Arthur, executed 1857-06-05, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 30)
    - Virginia: Tolson Bailey, executed 1918-07-02, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 31)
    - Virginia: Gabriel Battaile, executed 1906-06-08, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 32)
    - Virginia: Charles William Beaver, executed 1883-03-30, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 33)
    - Virginia: Aurelius Christian, executed 1909-02-19, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 34)
    - Virginia: Clem, executed 1787-05-11, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 35)
    - Virginia: John Eccles, executed 1910-11-11, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 36)
    - Virginia: Percy Ellis, executed 1916-03-16, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 37)
    - Virginia: Winston Green, executed 1908-10-30, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 38)
    - Virginia: Raleigh Haskins, executed 1921-09-30, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 39)
    - Virginia: Issac (Collerton), executed 1825-10-21, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 40)
    - Virginia: Steve Roach, executed 1999-08-25, 1996 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 41)
    - Virginia: Fritz Lewis, executed 1924-09-12, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 42)
    - Virginia: Sam Pannell, executed 1932-05-20, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 43)
    - Virginia: Harry Sitlington, executed 1910-12-17, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 44)
    - Virginia: Neal Standback, executed 1902-03-12, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 45)
    - Virginia: Douglas Christopher Thomas, executed 2000-01-10, 1991 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 46)
    - Virginia: Douglas Christopher Thomas, executed 2000-01-10, 1993 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 47)
    - Virginia: Douglas Christopher Thomas, executed 2000-01-10, 1993; 2007 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 48)
    - Virginia: Douglas Christopher Thomas, executed 2000-01-10, 1999 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 49)
    - Virginia: William (Colston), executed 1796-09-16, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 50)
    - Virginia: Dwayne Allen Wrights, executed 1998-10-14, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 51)
    - Washington: General, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 52)